zooloo.com 2010-08-15

# ZooLoo Privacy Policy - Your Name. Your Domain. Your Life.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
This policy covers how ZooLoo, along with its partners, (collectively, "ZooLoo," "we," "us," or "our") treats personal information that it collects and receives on ZooLoo.com. We are not in the business of selling information about you: we use information shared with us for the purpose of running and improving our services. This notice tells you what information we collect, steps we take to protect and secure it, how we use and share information, and finally, how you can contact us with questions or concerns.

**Information We Gather**  

  * ZooLoo collects personal information when you register with us, use ZooLoo products or services or post content on a ZooLoo web site. This information is typically limited to your email address, username, survey information and any information you post on your site. Your password is stored using a one way hash function.
  * ZooLoo may register a domain name and maintain ownership and control of it on your behalf. Any transfer of a domain name is subject to ZooLoo Terms of Service.
  * ZooLoo may also collect personal information if you enter into promotions or sweepstakes.
  * ZooLoo may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.
  * ZooLoo uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, support, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

**Billing Information**  

  * Should you sign up for any ZooLoo Paid Services including Upgrades/Add-Ons or register a domain through us, we require your billing information in order to process the transaction.
  * Should you sign up for a ZooLoo Plus account or register a domain through us, we require your billing information in order to process the transaction.
  * We use the Secure PayPal Merchant Services to execute your transaction.
  * We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.
  * If your subscription is auto-renewing, a recurring subscription will be created at our payment gateway and we store your billing information in our secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription.
  * Should you cancel your subscription, your billing information will be immediately removed by ZooLoo upon final reconciliation and settlement of your account.
  * All transactions are processed over an industry standard SSL/TLS connection, with a minimum of 128-bit encryption.

**IP Address**  

  * ZooLoo may occasionally obtain IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our web sites. IP addresses, browser and session information may be used for various purposes, including to: 
    * Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
    * Estimate the total number of users visiting ZooLoo's web sites from specific geographical regions.
    * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services or resources that we offer.
    * Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse.

**Cookies**  

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use ZooLoo services or products that require you to "sign in" and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings.
  * Most browsers allow you to configure it to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set.
  * ZooLoo uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: 
    * Require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.
    * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the ZooLoo Sites, Products and Services.
    * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
    * Conduct research to improve the content and services provided on the ZooLoo Sites, Products and Services.

**Information Relating to Children**  

  * Users under the age of 13 are prohibited by the site's Terms of Service from registering their own ZooLoo account. ZooLoo does not target users under the age of 13, knowingly collect information from users under the age of 13, or knowingly allow users under the age of 13 to register.

**Information Use, Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * ZooLoo does not share personal information we learn about you from your use of the ZooLoo web sites, products and services with others except as described in this policy.
  * ZooLoo may use or share your personal information where it is necessary to complete a transaction, to operate or improve the ZooLoo products and services, to outsource certain services to a trusted partner, to do something that you have asked us to do, or to develop aggregate information.
  * From time to time, ZooLoo may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest (collectively "promotion") on ZooLoo. You may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. Unless otherwise indicated in the promotion's rules, this information will be used strictly for the purpose of notifying and arranging delivery of promotional items to the person selected.
  * When you register for ZooLoo, we collect user-submitted account information such as username and email address to identify users and send notifications related to the use of the service.
  * When you post content on a ZooLoo web site you have the ability to post content which may include personally identifiable information about yourself. You are responsible for the information you post online, or you share with another website that you link to from ZooLoo, and you do so at your own risk.
  * If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return or other unwanted and possibly harmful contact.
  * ZooLoo may share personally identifiable information about you under the following circumstances: 
    * We may share your personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or, defend against legal claims and if in our judgment in such circumstances disclosure is required or appropriate.
    * We may share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
    * As we continue to develop our business, we may also buy or sell all or part of our business. In such transactions, personally identifiable information you have shared with us is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred. The transferred personally identifiable information will remain subject to the promises made in this privacy policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.

**Terms of Service**  
Your use of ZooLoo and its related services, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Service, the terms of which are incorporated into this Privacy Policy by reference. You should carefully review the Terms of Service.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
ZooLoo may revise, modify or update this privacy policy at anytime at our sole discretion. Changes to the privacy policy take effect immediately. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make efforts to ensure security on our systems.

  * We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.
  * Your account information is password-protected. Additionally, your account's password is stored using a one way hash algorithm.
  * In certain areas, ZooLoo uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If ZooLoo learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using ZooLoo or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of those sites, products and services. We may post a notice on our applicable web sites if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the applicable web sites. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you must notify us at info@ZooLoo.com.

**Changing your Preferences and Personal Information**  

  * You can edit your account information with ZooLoo at any time.
  * You can delete your applicable account by visiting the applicable account deletion page; however, please note that some personal information (e.g., your contact information) may remain in our records to the extent necessary to protect our legal interests or document compliance with regulatory requirements, or the information may be retained within aggregate information.

**Contacting ZooLoo**  
If you have a privacy concern regarding ZooLoo, or this policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of those sites, products or services, you should complete a feedback form or you can write to us by email at [info@ZooLoo.com](mailto:info@zooloo.com).

Last Revised: January 2010

^ back to top
